I love when people demonstrate the capability of humanity to show up for each other.
And I especially love when they do it slang and curses, left and right, holding a black and mild.
This is not right at all.
Hey, bro, where are your people at?
Huh? You okay?
I'm okay.
You okay?
Come on, let's go home.
I'm going to take you home, okay?
I'm good.
Come on.
Come on, dude.
You okay?
Yeah.
Okay.
I got you.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
You can turn around and go back the way you came.
Why?
What?
What do you mean?
He's wet.
What are you talking about?
He just is not supposed to be out here.
He's going to go all the way back the way he's supposed to go.
Where is he supposed to go?
Don't he live here?
He knows.
He knows what?
Where are you supposed to go?
Are you supposed to be out here?
No.
Well, why would you make him go way back down there?
To teach him.
It's like...
To teach him what?
Yeah, that's what happens when you get old.
You have things like that.
You don't know what you're talking about.
No, I do know what I'm talking about.
You have no idea.
Yeah, I know exactly.
Yeah, I'm about to mind yours.
Because I know you fucking just using him for a check, you piece of shit.
You got this man doing his shit and his pampers.
Are you kidding?
I'll call the fucking police right now.
I'll call the fucking police.
That man in a fucking pampers wet.
And you're going to make him go back down the street, you stupid motherfucker.
What do you mean the way you need to walk?
I'm calling the fucking police, you stupid piece of shit.
Thank you for all the love and all the support.
And I just talked to a detective about an hour ago.
So, I sent him the video.
So, I mean, she's definitely being investigated.
It was the sheriff's department that called me.
So, you know, I'm just thankful to everybody that showed her love.
I just, it's a sad situation.
But hopefully, you just get put in a better situation.
So, thank you for all the love.
Big ups to this brother, man.
Shout out to you.
Thank you.